<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Apple</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="titlerecipe">Ostrich</string>
    <string name="shortDescriptionRecipe">This recipe does not tell you how to make any food. It is
        just dicking (Dutch: lullen) about randdom this you know. Just to see how the layout works
        out.</string>
    <string name="information">\
        Environment\n\n
    Water footprint\n\n
    Carbon footprint\n\n
        Time\n\n
        Difficulty\n\n
        Price\n\n
        Rating
    </string>
    <string name="ingredients">There are several ingredients:\n
    1 chicken\n
    500g of shoes\n
    50 lbs of marmalade\n
    600 l of liquid nitrogen\n
    2 nucreal reactors for power</string>
    <string name="instruction">1. Use the nuclear reactors to cut the shoes. Only use half the shoe for
    dinner, use the other half to hide the nuclear  waste you just produced. Let simmer for 2 minutes.\n\n
    2. Use the marmalade to catch some ants. Then use them to clean the wounds that were caused by the
    high amounts of radiation.\n\n
    3. Die from radiation disease. If everyone died but you, use the nitrogen to freeze yourself and
    die happily ever after.</string>

    <string name="environmentInformation"> Environmental Rating\n
        Producing food has a certain impact
        on the environment. For examples, to create farmland huge forests are cut down, to grow crops
        a lot of fertilizers and pesticides are used, animals are treated with hormones and antibiotics
        which pollute the land and water, create antibiotic resistances and can cause harm in humans,
        water resources are being depleted for irrigation, the fish populations are nearly depleted and
        food production and transportation set free a lot of greenhouse gas emissions.\n\n
        The environmental rating includes all these aspects and creates a weighted rating of the environmental
        impact of the dish.\n\n
        In general products from animal origin have a higher environmental impact, because animals require
        more space and water than crops. They also require crops as food and medical treatments. These all
        lead to a lower environmental rating.
</string>

    <string name="informationWaterFootprint">
        Water footprint\n
        The water footprint indicates how much water is needed to create a certain product,
        in this case the specific meal. Included in the water footprint are all the steps from production,
        transportation and final usage. \n\n
        For food the most important factor is the water used in the production, especially when growing crops. 
        The other factors are compared to this neglectable low. When producing meat a lot of crops need 
        to be grown to feed the animals. Because the feed conversion efficiency is low, animals need to 
        eat much more crops than they produce meat. Thus to produce meat more water is needed than to produce 
        crops.\n\n
        The table below shows an overview of the water usage of different types of diets. To create one 
        kCal of food from animal origin 2.5 L of water are used, for food from vegetable origin 0.5 L 
        are used.        
    </string>
    
    <string name="informationCarbonFootprint">
        Carbon footprint\n
        The carbon footprint measures all greenhouse gases that are released when
        producing a certain product, in this case a dish. It is usually expressed in equivalents of 
        carbon dioxide. The carbon footprint includes all steps, from production, transportation and 
        final usage.\n\n
        Different types of food produce different amounts of greenhouse emissions (GHE). Worldwide 
        15% of all GHE are due to agriculture. Products from animal origin produce more GHE than from
        vegetable.
    </string>

    <string name="informationTime">
        Time\n
        The time includes the total cooking time, including preparations.\n\n

        Ratings:\n
		1 clock: 0 – a minutes\n
		2 clocks : b – c minutes\n
		3 clocks : d – e minutes\n
		4 clocks : f – g minutes\n
		5 clocks : more than h minutes

    </string>
    
    <string name="informationDifficulty">
        Difficulty\n
        The rating for the difficulty gives an indication of how difficult is recipe is
        to make. A rating of 1 means it is a very easy recipe and is suitable for beginners. A rating 
        of 5 is given for the most difficult recipes.
    </string>
    
    <string name="informationPrice">
        Price\n
        The price rating includes the prices of all the ingredients used based on an average
        price for a certain ingredient. The rating takes into account the exact amounts used. The price
        is given per person.\n\n

		Ratings:\n
		1 coin: 0 – a €\n
		2 coins: b – c €\n
		3 coins: d – e €\n
		4 coins: f – g €\n
		5 coins: more than h €
    </string>
    
    <string name="informationRanking">
        Rating\n
        The rating shows the average of all the ratings people who use this app have given the
        recipe.
    </string>
</resources>
